(Penny:)I'm gonna need
more information.
(Sheldon:)Nothing odd.
(Sheldon:)I just wanted
to rub Amy's nose in it.
(Penny:)Okay, look, I might
be overreacting,
(Penny:)but how am I supposed
to get past this
(Penny:)when I know tomorrow
you're gonna go to work
(Penny:)and see this woman?
(Sheldon:)Forgive me for eavesdropping,
(Sheldon:)but as I see it,
there's a simple solution.
(Leonard:)Wake up, wake up, wake up.
(Sheldon:)Bring Penny to meet Mandy.
(Leonard:)What? Why?
(Sheldon:)Well, right now, Penny's
imagination is running wild,
(Sheldon:)but if they meet,
that will eliminate
(Sheldon:)the mystery
and alleviate her fears.
(Sheldon:)Like when that Sparkletts guy
let me look under his eye patch.
(Leonard:)Uh, first of all,
you made that guy cry.
(Sheldon:)And we learned that you don't
need an eyeball to do that.
(Leonard:)Secondly, I can't think
of a more horrible idea
(Leonard:)than Penny meeting Mandy.
(Penny:)Really? Why is that?